{
  "1": {
    "question": "2000003103200300000200210",
    "answer": "2244433143234332444212212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "3200200030302010100020031",
    "answer": "3223231332322412144423331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "2200500544402104030350004000560204053013350020015",
    "answer": "2255555544422154633355664445566224553613353322315",
    "size": 7
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "4100014020204002021240040400005000004044000060226",
    "answer": "4155514425254442421244544426655556664444666666226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "0050200002400021600020400400120600502500005000001",
    "answer": "5555221522444421666622444462126656552565555556661",
    "size": 7
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "0041000202000003020004300",
    "answer": "4441242232344333422134333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "0202102000040300002024010",
    "answer": "3212132324343342422424414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "3300000020423440400000014",
    "answer": "3344432422423444433442214",
    "size": 5
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "0403310003012000010022031",
    "answer": "4443314243312443313422331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "2000314401044006350000000031403503010050440004104",
    "answer": "2233314461544446356664635631463563316656444444144",
    "size": 7
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "0040212002010302003410100",
    "answer": "4444212232214342443414144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "1020020130030300103030001",
    "answer": "1322423134234343143433441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "5550500006003003032004020101003405001005000010133",
    "answer": "5555522666663363332234422151433445541345532214133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "0102032100000000043103040",
    "answer": "3122432144323341343133444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "0300050003101010420020200301610033005000000002000",
    "answer": "2355555233141212424426242341614433465555546662244",
    "size": 7
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "5055200014040400004000230160003000040305500056105",
    "answer": "5555224514446442664644236164453656645365565556155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "0021031003200023001203200",
    "answer": "3321331233224423441233221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "0352201600060403401600000000054055050300055033250",
    "answer": "6352261635566463451646645664654455455312555533251",
    "size": 7
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "2000023002010033223100000",
    "answer": "2334223442314333223134444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "0026020000005401000204030300000013100010051210000",
    "answer": "6226224666655441555244533324455513142513351215555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "0002330103300011020222000",
    "answer": "3422334133342411424222442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "4000003610300003003010000260034023200000030450005",
    "answer": "4446633614366363633616366262634623264466336455555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "1010100300200100010031033",
    "answer": "1413124334244143314431333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "3400310300420200010560100050240600030440050310055",
    "answer": "3433312344425236612562166556246656634446653315555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "4400041004160000100460564240450020000644004500021",
    "answer": "4466641244164625166464564246456426645644264566621",
    "size": 7
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "3203330030000200510216023030012000000040310260030",
    "answer": "3223332335555266512216623332612466264446312266633",
    "size": 7
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "0120004440332003000203505053050006005550556000550",
    "answer": "4122444444332433553233565553656666365556556666555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "1301000200010120010010200",
    "answer": "1331343233412124413212233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "0435021040501404050400105060060102044040405505540",
    "answer": "4435221643561464356446155664666162244446445555544",
    "size": 7
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "2230200002130213000030133",
    "answer": "2233233432134213442333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "2444344260400450051000005000005500450010551233555",
    "answer": "2444344266433455651245665521565544452314551233555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "3003100301301500000206330335040000034035010033005",
    "answer": "3223155331331566662256336335343132234435513433555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "0010200002430100220000010",
    "answer": "4314243442434144224433314",
    "size": 5
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "2030040000604100440030450160600230033010000300404",
    "answer": "2233444663664164446636452163665236333513341355444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "1021000030201000203000120",
    "answer": "1321423234231343223433122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "3134004050100000065006500056001300000030406004441",
    "answer": "3134444353156635365566566656651365665336466664441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "1200224023000041403340040300000402120100500000031",
    "answer": "1233224423555441453344545324454452125155552553331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "3200005000006542505030010500406051366000004000031",
    "answer": "3225555336666542555634216563446651366613224444331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "0300122002101000000102103",
    "answer": "3334122442141424443122133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "0200001022000300202201400",
    "answer": "2244441422423334242241444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "0022303443000001324022100",
    "answer": "4422343443432431324122122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "4442030000003050102000100201005310450005400100034",
    "answer": "4442233466663556162555133251525315452555445153334",
    "size": 7
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "1010030010200310000000212",
    "answer": "1313333413244312433212212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "4001002300002000033001004",
    "answer": "4231242332442212333421444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "2000300100300100000223002",
    "answer": "2444323143334132444223332",
    "size": 5
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "4003100004500000005051000500301056100303032005030",
    "answer": "4333155444566566655651366565331656125333632555533",
    "size": 7
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "0006000020031004221001000020033301300050020030401",
    "answer": "4266666423331644221231555523533351355554223334441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "6055010200000000502203050350001334204010000000300",
    "answer": "6655615265666526562253656355361334234414424433341",
    "size": 7
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "2040003003043204001000102",
    "answer": "2444423323143234441322122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "0300100340210210330040010",
    "answer": "1344123344212214333244412",
    "size": 5
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "5200300000322000000046522400030100000300400004250",
    "answer": "5223344556322465666646522465633144566342456444255",
    "size": 7
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "0013003000000202302010204",
    "answer": "2213313443234242342412244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "0210001020030100210000031",
    "answer": "2212441324433144213442331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "5055500100020021063400030300031504600500030021203",
    "answer": "5555566166622621663462336346131534655552431221233",
    "size": 7
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "0000031201302300000220220",
    "answer": "3444431231342322443224221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "3300002042003002301000022",
    "answer": "3331212242233442341444422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "3201003000001220100000330",
    "answer": "3221433444441224144443334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "2030012505010050000462020000002100000005013015540",
    "answer": "2233312555514256644462626666262154636655413315544",
    "size": 7
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "1200002003010300321000000",
    "answer": "1244442433412344321443344",
    "size": 5
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "4022001541050300305600032500064050050402146004204",
    "answer": "4422661541556354335635632563564256456442146664244",
    "size": 7
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "0102404100030200041014040",
    "answer": "4122444144432243341214442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "1000120230032011000200001",
    "answer": "1444124233232311332244441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "0010001020104100024003000",
    "answer": "3312331423144133424433244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "1030000024001203003112200",
    "answer": "1334434324341243443112233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "0003002203301000001031020",
    "answer": "4443342243341443441431422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "0300300300555220600420005000520020462130030060020",
    "answer": "3355333366555222666425555644523323462132336666622",
    "size": 7
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "0300032010210330404100030",
    "answer": "3344432214213332444114333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "0020000000014010050602050101355601000000230000050",
    "answer": "6224446666614616556662256161355661336662233555553",
    "size": 7
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "2000101012001302100100000",
    "answer": "2233131312331322133124444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "3040160000400035641006500012005524400060000330103",
    "answer": "3644166366466635641626566212655524466664431333133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "1240240010000000400330322",
    "answer": "1244242412414314413333322",
    "size": 5
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "0300000212003012130000002",
    "answer": "4333242212443312134224442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "3002233030020300302131003",
    "answer": "3442233431224333322131333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "3201000024200003100000003",
    "answer": "3221433424224243143433433",
    "size": 5
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "0030301106503004050400405040500060204022010330120",
    "answer": "3335331166563454656445465642546566254622615333122",
    "size": 7
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "0300240100100040020440020",
    "answer": "4333244142142444121444422",
    "size": 5
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "0201000030210301003003120",
    "answer": "1221424434214341343433122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "0000100100030002130000520053010306000020100400130",
    "answer": "5555155125335352136535522653513366654326134442133",
    "size": 7
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "4060133400004000434414044103655550006000034440201",
    "answer": "4666133464334346434414644143655555366666134444221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "3200420024001400003000043010401024062040000000050",
    "answer": "3244422324551435553444443314421224562644456666555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "1001003100004200001021201",
    "answer": "1221433124344242441421221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "0003101024100000101000300",
    "answer": "2333121424144242141423334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "0201001400200010013002040",
    "answer": "1221221432244311413422444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "6000004022003200040000343030303400200344021030100",
    "answer": "6664444622333266444123343331343455244344521434155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "1320000310002000310000313",
    "answer": "1322443314422444313343313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "3032000041020102400004401",
    "answer": "3332244441122132413324441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "0435005400020555012530000000133301330600013004440",
    "answer": "4435555443321555512535515553133351336666613364444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "0040000604620020402020043134022000005000503060000",
    "answer": "6646666664623226462322643134322334435555543666666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "4040000400005033000061220344200005404000010000306",
    "answer": "4446666435555633533461225344245555424666614433366",
    "size": 7
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "0003030402120546302054000001103046450226040505000",
    "answer": "4623335462125546342554634661163446456226645555644",
    "size": 7
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "0000000210004000320204201",
    "answer": "2123323213434424324244241",
    "size": 5
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "0020003004410423003000300",
    "answer": "4422443344413423313231331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "0012002030030300402002100",
    "answer": "1212232334334344442422124",
    "size": 5
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "0151004200022002206300000003035040440030301300001",
    "answer": "2151444255522442256334666663435544443533341355221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "1000403200060420550000220540000610220100035050002",
    "answer": "1444433266663425556646225544666612222163335555522",
    "size": 7
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "0200423100000100003010102",
    "answer": "1224423144233134443314122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "1005000401224340006440055600422000113331030005005",
    "answer": "1555533451224346666444555664422553113331332255555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "0132000010100032001013001",
    "answer": "2132223313144432241313331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "0100040032210002000101004005462000000400231006120",
    "answer": "3144445332215522666151664445462264344466231666123",
    "size": 7
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "2212000301020000210230302",
    "answer": "2212244331423444214233342",
    "size": 5
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "1040042360000003201300004305106000040400010105000",
    "answer": "1644442366666233221354444335166655544466614155555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "2600302000100240254350050400455440540060006040041",
    "answer": "2666332262131246254354655435455443546666556644441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "2233003002000002003001232",
    "answer": "2233333422344312423221232",
    "size": 5
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "3200400000320120000020034",
    "answer": "3224431442322122144423334",
    "size": 5
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "0006000100003032001010050000154100000060000000504",
    "answer": "6666661125553332561313356654154165455466545544554",
    "size": 7
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "0605000050240005330420000000220323000630200002020",
    "answer": "6665555652244565333426555242226323366633236622121",
    "size": 7
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "0040042006000040333442000140440003000610050020101",
    "answer": "4644442466666244333442266144446333546615554622151",
    "size": 7
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "1024000200030313000010032",
    "answer": "1424444244434313343214432",
    "size": 5
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "4000012130000000023001000",
    "answer": "4444312133424444423441233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "0004001023143033500100400040040054504432405001000",
    "answer": "1334431223143333554153415545543354554432455551245",
    "size": 7
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "0001033430000330000505200020010510004000000060050",
    "answer": "4441633436666333655515225225514516554446655566655",
    "size": 7
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "4030100023013003000001021",
    "answer": "4432144323313433444331221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "4045200502000000030000050126000502056005100301021",
    "answer": "4445226542555656233565653126565552656665163331221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "3040003000006102000504000303000321040300004001600",
    "answer": "3444333346666132655554265333455321645332664551666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "2060002000000000000000035300641012600002104440100",
    "answer": "2666662243556264353366435326641512666622164444166",
    "size": 7
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "3210000020000010200303010",
    "answer": "3213332423344212243333313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "3001000220030400102010000",
    "answer": "3331444224433444132214444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "0201002014200005010005005005164010100000005000420",
    "answer": "5221662514226255416665645555164615156664445555422",
    "size": 7
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "0120000502013050055355600030031002303325006000010",
    "answer": "5123355562313556655355666535531252363325236666613",
    "size": 7
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "0032000014030301400004200",
    "answer": "3332244414433341441444224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "3000000210430300100102200",
    "answer": "3334442214433344144142244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "0000000001000634044501030022013046002200004050220",
    "answer": "3466666341555634344551435422413546642256664455226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "2030020001133300001010300",
    "answer": "2433324441133324441214333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "6050000020505602060100100020040303024040200000305",
    "answer": "6656666625555662666166166225646333524442252133355",
    "size": 7
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "0023403000030300001012400",
    "answer": "4323443234434344241412441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "3000030223010401320200002",
    "answer": "3444334223314431324233242",
    "size": 5
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "1500063305500000005030404500505000560000004000034",
    "answer": "1556663335566353545635444555555664566663444444334",
    "size": 7
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "4200102103000000031001001",
    "answer": "4244142143443432331321221",
    "size": 5
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "1412000200650020400046004005300060200420020001441",
    "answer": "1412244246655424466546614655364464236422423661441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "0060001505522005000002002204100430034405020002100",
    "answer": "6666661555522425666442662234164433234455523322155",
    "size": 7
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "0220020033000063405030040504500056055455035500000",
    "answer": "6226223633664363465436646544564656355455635566663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "0002000010533000350602315000064052000040130003301",
    "answer": "6662236616533663356662315623264552366444136663331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "3020000014310244400000301",
    "answer": "3422434414314244432444331",
    "size": 5
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "0200240002030001023000043",
    "answer": "4224244342433441223344443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "1031003000020000002310301",
    "answer": "1331443444422334432313321",
    "size": 5
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "1001000130010002023010001",
    "answer": "1441444134212342423414441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "0250060026055003040400605040050503001606600500550",
    "answer": "1255666326555633644466665546655533321666662555556",
    "size": 7
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "0500000050416064006500204050024005301450500000050",
    "answer": "6555566654416664466566214656624465361456535555653",
    "size": 7
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "1000042030001001500002060004101030020213000100063",
    "answer": "1344442335551221554442666364161636326213632126663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "2000320021001001300300010",
    "answer": "2433324221441431344333413",
    "size": 5
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "1003200060121002000066250333200006006660300024004",
    "answer": "1333266666121662656666255333255666126663331224444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "0100000230102040043001200",
    "answer": "2133424234142442443321223",
    "size": 5
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "5000056023320040000000101000002333040000506001201",
    "answer": "5555256523325642355564121666462333546655556661221",
    "size": 7
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "2300100000004500154006100404542000000000600000000",
    "answer": "2333155266644566154556125464542556454445645556664",
    "size": 7
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "4010000542144000002460000000551000004521320000501",
    "answer": "4416666542144654232465133241551233244521324455551",
    "size": 7
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "5310230000030503150000002060010010002204000000020",
    "answer": "5312235535533553155655522565614416562244666666226",
    "size": 7
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "0301033530401003004400230020003340520004330010043",
    "answer": "5351333535441553554455235225523345525554332515443",
    "size": 7
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "0102020013000000320240012",
    "answer": "2122323413434434324244212",
    "size": 5
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "0514042000000050505240603020135010400000001602230",
    "answer": "5514442566664256555245653324135314433666631662233",
    "size": 7
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "0030000012313010000201000",
    "answer": "4333244412313313443231442",
    "size": 5
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "3330000002060520201003044455364555130014021224441",
    "answer": "3335555262666526261663644455364555136614221224441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "0200110323303000020000200",
    "answer": "2232114323343433424334244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "6043255040004000124400000000033420004000601333101",
    "answer": "6443255643324564124456132465633426664442661333161",
    "size": 7
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "2100000202303000030000013",
    "answer": "2124224242343433434334313",
    "size": 5
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "0003120032000100210101000",
    "answer": "2433124432324123214131444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "2120100310100000021300100",
    "answer": "2122123314134443221333133",
    "size": 5
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "2130000002040201000000141",
    "answer": "2133224432442211344433141",
    "size": 5
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "0420100100100100030004121",
    "answer": "4422144144133144432444121",
    "size": 5
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "0000001031302002003020100",
    "answer": "3444431231342342443424144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "0260000003000010151000022302010000110000000232400",
    "answer": "2266666333555614151524422332415553113325542232444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "1506000004040102010200004043000004000031203230400",
    "answer": "1566666554446152412235254443355554332331223234444",
    "size": 7
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "0102100000310210000041030",
    "answer": "3122134444312214443241332",
    "size": 5
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "0020013000000000034036434001001050020310320120033",
    "answer": "6622513644555364334536434441631555223315322122533",
    "size": 7
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "0120120030001203002001010",
    "answer": "2122123334341243442431414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "0002600050030064044300033010040310304060020033002",
    "answer": "5522666655433664544366433416646313364666326333662",
    "size": 7
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "3203001303000001031004041",
    "answer": "3223331343323441231444441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "1003000022210001223200010",
    "answer": "1433324422214331223233312",
    "size": 5
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "0300112000020100002310040",
    "answer": "3334112443324133322314444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "3033310300555036500600013300030066503630050221305",
    "answer": "3633316365555636566666613335636666533633651221355",
    "size": 7
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "0030300001313422000040400",
    "answer": "3133334441313422233244441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "5000440051400004001355050503143002000031200120006",
    "answer": "5224445551455554451355455533143352633231263126666",
    "size": 7
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "0124103040000000302022330",
    "answer": "4124143242434424322122333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "0010600010510003100221050500000610600020301010030",
    "answer": "2216666315516633155221556566556616656623361612136",
    "size": 7
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "0000020331040402120100000",
    "answer": "2444423331144442122124444",
    "size": 5
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "0230010002030100030010204",
    "answer": "2233314442234122334412244",
    "size": 5
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "1200300100002030100140120",
    "answer": "1224333143432434124144122",
    "size": 5
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "0100032134000100000012030",
    "answer": "3133432134324144443412233",
    "size": 5
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "0400330020044003150050102020400152003300300140010",
    "answer": "4443335422444533155453122525443152543345334144413",
    "size": 7
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "0000210010230210400230000",
    "answer": "4444213312232212444233342",
    "size": 5
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "3000101020003300030001200",
    "answer": "3444131422343344434441224",
    "size": 5
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "2204600030043000302000420230002040005500100042031",
    "answer": "2244666433443644312365424236552444245523124442331",
    "size": 7
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "0026101000024013302000600060003056101500003036600",
    "answer": "6226141666624413332426666562633356161555623336662",
    "size": 7
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "0020014000313000001001001",
    "answer": "4422414434313343441431441",
    "size": 5
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "0000203012302300030010100",
    "answer": "4444233212342344433414144",
    "size": 5
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "0040000004001600641000500500033303406000500202201",
    "answer": "5646666564461656641345566534633353466665542262251",
    "size": 7
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "0015050300060530051000330640004100440500040303500",
    "answer": "3515555356666535551661333644444166445555641333566",
    "size": 7
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "0020020010102300400002201",
    "answer": "2322423314122344443442231",
    "size": 5
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "0202050044305001005510414440646006004055300401050",
    "answer": "2242251644335561435516414444646666364655336461555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "2301004020000000201002033",
    "answer": "2331424324344243241432333",
    "size": 5
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "2204103020000000202044021",
    "answer": "2244133422324334212344421",
    "size": 5
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "2002003001301200000004210",
    "answer": "2442223441331224423344213",
    "size": 5
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "1200003024000004303000043",
    "answer": "1224443124434244343341443",
    "size": 5
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "4003220000040033300000100640004410604600335001003",
    "answer": "4333226444644633366465166646544416654666335561663",
    "size": 7
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "0013004200000303012000021",
    "answer": "4413444234332343412444421",
    "size": 5
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "1006000033202200001601500002022000005000050300041",
    "answer": "1366666533262255521661566662522555255544555333441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "3022030034002004100404404",
    "answer": "3422134434342344123444414",
    "size": 5
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "2200441050000014004050600030505002500000102540041",
    "answer": "2244441555553514444356666635555622525333152544441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "0001300010022540300306002030020203050540100004001",
    "answer": "4431333413622546366356662635626263552546155554441",
    "size": 7
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "2003550010000544040001330262000101240000600355005",
    "answer": "2333555216666544442651333262444161243666663355555",
    "size": 7
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "1000010012014564000000043000400300000130020100402",
    "answer": "1444415612214564445456643545466354544135524144442",
    "size": 7
  }
}